Guide to the Duke Real Estate Office records, 1893-2018 and undated UA.10.04.0007
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Real Estate Deeds, 1893-2018; undated
  - File No.: 181, Grantee: Dolian Haris, Grantor: I. A. Burnette, Type: Deed, 1924 April 30 (Box 4)
    County: Durham, Conveyed by File No.: 209, Deed Book: 70, Page: 71, Comments/Location: E/S 7th Street
  - File No.: 182, Grantee: Dolian Haris, Grantor: T. L. McClees, Type: Deed, 1924 April 23 (Box 4)
    County: Durham, Conveyed by File No.: 209, Deed Book: 70, Page: 56, Comments/Location: E/S 6th Street
  - File No.: 183, Grantee: Dolian Haris, Grantor: T. L. McClees, Type: Deed, 1924 April 24 (Box 4)
    County: Durham, Conveyed by File No.: 209, Deed Book: 71, Page: 425, Comments/Location: E/S 6th Street
  - File No.: 184, Grantee: Dolian Haris, Grantor: Jno Manning, Type: Deed, 1924 May 12 (Box 4)
    County: Durham, Conveyed by File No.: 209, Deed Book: 71, Page: 438, Comments/Location: S/S Green Street, Old/New File No.: 184
  - File No.: 185, Grantee: Dolian Haris, Grantor: C. H. Johns, Type: Deed, 1924 June 10 (Box 5)
    County: Durham, Conveyed by File No.: 209, Deed Book: 70, Page: 135, Comments/Location: E/S 6th Street
  - File No.: 186, Grantee: Dolian Haris, Grantor: Cecil McClees, Sr., Type: Deed, 1924 June 11 (Box 5)
    County: Durham, Conveyed by File No.: 209, Deed Book: 70, Page: 159, Comments/Location: E/S 6th Street
  - File No.: 187, Grantee: Dolian Haris, Grantor: Florence Shaw, Type: Deed, 1924 June 9 (Box 5)
    County: Durham, Conveyed by File No.: 209, Deed Book: 70, Page: 157, Comments/Location: Sedgefield
  - File No.: 188, Grantee: Dolian Haris, Grantor: Lillian Randall, Type: Deed, 1924 June 12 (Box 5)
    County: Durham, Conveyed by File No.: 209, Deed Book: 70, Page: 186, Comments/Location: 6th Street & Markham Street
  - File No.: 189, Grantee: Dolian Haris, Grantor: G. W. Lewis, Type: Deed, 1924 June 17 (Box 5)
    County: Durham, Conveyed by File No.: 209, Deed Book: 70, Page: 170, Comments/Location: W/S 6th Street
  - File No.: 190, Grantee: Dolian Haris, Grantor: Luvina White, Type: Deed, 1924 June 11 (Box 5)
    County: Durham, Conveyed by File No.: 209, Deed Book: 70, Page: 134, Comments/Location: E/S 6th Street
  - File No.: 192, Grantee: Dolian Harris, Grantor: Thomas Atwood, Type: Deed, 1928 June 23 (Box 5)
    County: Durham, Conveyed by File No.: 209, Deed Book: 70, Page: 208, Comments/Location: E/S 7th Street
  - File No.: 194, Grantee: Dolian Harris, Grantor: A. H. McDonald, Type: Deed, 1924 June 25 (Box 5)
    County: Durham, Conveyed by File No.: 209, Deed Book: 71, Page: 513, Comments/Location: E/S 7th Street
  - File No.: 195, Grantee: Dolian Harris, Grantor: A. J. Parker, Type: Deed, 2024 June 9 (Box 5)
    County: Durham, Conveyed by File No.: 209, Deed Book: 70, Page: 233, Comments/Location: E/S 7th Street
  - File No.: 197, Grantee: Dolian Harris, Grantor: J. R. Jones, Type: Deed, 1924 June 27 (Box 5)
    County: Durham, Conveyed by File No.: 209, Deed Book: 70, Page: 224, Comments/Location: E/S Seventh Street
  - File No.: 201, Grantee: Dolian Harris, Grantor: John Harris & Others, Type: Deed, 1924 October 17 (Box 5)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 72, Page: 88, Comments/Location: Buchanan Boulevard
  - File No.: 202, Grantee: Dolian Harris, Grantor: Captolia Harris, Type: Deed, 1924 October 25 (Box 5)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 72, Page: 98, Comments/Location: Buchanan Boulevard
  - File No.: 203, Grantee: Dolian Harris, Grantor: J. Plato Griffin, Type: Deed, 1924 October 25 (Box 5)
    County: Durham, Conveyed by File No.: 210, Deed Book: 70, Page: 663, Comments/Location: Green & Sedgefield
  - File No.: 204, Grantee: Dolian Harris, Grantor: I. G. Sigmon, Type: Deed, 1924 October 29 (Box 5)
    County: Durham, Conveyed by File No.: 210, Deed Book: 70, Page: 689, Comments/Location: Sedgefield
  - File No.: 205 and 206, Grantee: Dolian Harris, Grantor: Julia McKinney, Type: Deed, 1924 October 31 (Box 5)
    County: Durham, Conveyed by File No.: 210, Deed Book: 73, Page: 1, Comments/Location: Sedgefield & Green
  - File No.: 206, Grantee: Dolian Harris, Grantor: Bertha Holder Snipes, Type: Deed, 1924 October 31 (Box 5)
    County: Durham, Conveyed by File No.: 210, Deed Book: 73, Page: 6, Comments/Location: Sedgefield & Green
  - File No.: 207, Grantee: Dolian Harris, Grantor: D. M. Sharpe, Type: Deed, 1924 October 28 (Box 5)
    County: Durham, Conveyed by File No.: 210, Deed Book: 73, Page: 27, Comments/Location: Sedgefield
  - File No.: 208, Grantee: Dolian Harris, Grantor: Celia Truman & Others, Type: Deed, 1924 October 31 (Box 5)
    County: Durham, Conveyed by File No.: 210, Deed Book: 72, Page: 139, Comments/Location: Markham
  - File No.: 209, Grantee: Trinity College, Grantor: Dolian Harris, Type: Deed, 1924 July 8 (Box 5)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 71, Page: 541, Comments/Location: Various Lots
  - File No.: 210, Grantee: Trinity College, Grantor: Dolian Harris, Type: Deed, 1924 November 17 (Box 5)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 72, Page: 141, Comments/Location: 5 lots; Markham, Green, Sedgefield
  - File No.: 211, Grantee: Trinity College, Grantor: W. L. Wilkerson, Type: Deed, 1924 August 7 (Box 5)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 70, Page: 394, Comments/Location: Green & Berkeley
  - File No.: 212, Grantee: Trinity College, Grantor: Thomas McClees, Type: Deed, 1924 August 7 (Box 5)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 72, Page: 33, Comments/Location: Green & Sedgefield
  - File No.: 213, Grantee: Trinity College, Grantor: Luvina White & Duke Land, Type: Deed, 1924 July 15 (Box 5)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 71, Page: 559, Comments/Location: Green & Berkeley
  - File No.: 214, Grantee: Trinity College, Grantor: Jennie Thomas, Type: Deed, 1924 June 18 (Box 5)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 71, Page: 527, Comments/Location: Sixth & Markham Streets
  - File No.: 215, Grantee: Trinity College, Grantor: James M. Parker, Executor, Type: Deed, 1924 June 24 (Box 5)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 71, Page: 519, Comments/Location: Sixth & Markham Streets
  - File No.: 216, Grantee: Trinity College, Grantor: W. M. Durham, Type: Deed, 1924 May 16 (Box 5)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 70, Page: 91, Comments/Location: Markham Street
  - File No.: 217, Grantee: Trinity College, Grantor: J. S. Carr, Type: Deed, 1893 May 11 (Box 5)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 13, Page: 335-336, Comments/Location: Guess Mill Road
  - File No.: 218, Grantee: Trinity College, Grantor: City of Durham, Type: Deed, 1916 June 12 (Box 5)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 1, Page: 277, Comments/Location: Maplewood Cemetery
  - File No.: 219, Grantee: Trinity College, Grantor: G. W. Burch, Type: Deed, 1899 December 18 (Box 5)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 22, Page: 50-51, Comments/Location: Guess Road Area
  - File No.: 220, Grantee: Trinity College, Grantor: B. N. Duke, Type: Deed, 1900 May 31 (Box 5)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 71, Page: 521, Comments/Location: Markham & Sedgefield Streets
  - File No.: 221, Grantee: J. H. Southgate, et al, Grantor: Lucy Cunningham, Type: Deed, 2001 March 30 (Box 6)
    Deeds in the Real Estate Office are copies of public records, and are open for research. Additional materials under administrative restriction until 2026.
  - File No.: 222, Grantee: Trinity College, Grantor: Trinity Land Co., Type: Deed, 2001 June 27 (Box 6)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 25, Page: 252, Comments/Location: Green Street
  - File No.: 223, Grantee: Trinity College, Grantor: B. N. Duke, Type: Deed, 2006 May 22 (Box 6)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 35, Page: 169, Comments/Location: Guess & Trinity
  - File No.: 224, Grantee: Trinity College, Grantor: J. A. Long, Type: Deed, 2007 November 12 (Box 6)
    Deeds in the Real Estate Office are copies of public records, and are open for research. Additional materials under administrative restriction until 2032.
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 37, Page: 397, Comments/Location: Markham Street
  - File No.: 225, Grantee: W. W. Flowers, Grantor: Trinity College, Type: Deed, 2008 February 5 (Box 6)
    Deeds in the Real Estate Office are copies of public records, and are open for research. Additional materials under administrative restriction until 2033.
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 37, Page: 454, Comments/Location: Trinity Avenue
  - File No.: 226, Grantee: J. J. Wolfe, Grantor: Trinity College, Type: Deed, 2008 May 25 (Box 6)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 37, Page: 554, Comments/Location: Markham Street
  - File No.: 227, Grantee: Trinity College, Grantor: C. W. Edwards, Type: Deed, 2009 April 2 (Box 6)
    Deeds in the Real Estate Office are copies of public records, and are open for research. Additional materials under administrative restriction until 2034.
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 41, Page: 298, Comments/Location: E/S Guess Road
  - File No.: 228, Grantee: Trinity College, Grantor: Trinity Land Co., Type: Deed, 2011 March 30 (Box 6)
    Deeds in the Real Estate Office are copies of public records, and are open for research. Additional materials under administrative restriction until 2036.
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 44, Page: 30, Comments/Location: West Main Street
  - File No.: 229, Grantee: W. H. Wannamaker, Grantor: Trinity College, Type: Deed, 2015 September 2 (Box 6)
    Deeds in the Real Estate Office are copies of public records, and are open for research. Additional materials under administrative restriction until 2040.
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 50, Page: 180, Comments/Location: Part of Lot 1, B.N. Duke Land/Guess Road
  - File No.: 230, Grantee: Trinity College, Grantor: W.L. Foushee, Truman Fam., Type: Deed, 2016 April 1 (Box 6)
    Deeds in the Real Estate Office are copies of public records, and are open for research. Additional materials under administrative restriction until 2041.
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 50, Page: 440, Comments/Location: Markham Street
  - File No.: 231, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: M.S. Llewellyn, Type: Deed, 1925 October 16 (Box 6)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 78, Page: 592, Comments/Location: Watts St., & Gloria Ave.
  - File No.: 232, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Robert Flowers, Type: Deed, 1926 April 26 (Box 6)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 122, Page: 225, Comments/Location: Pearson & Craven Avenues
  - File No.: 233, Grantee: W.Durham Methodist Church, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1926 June 28 (Box 6)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 83, Page: 483, Comments/Location: Sixth Street
  - File No.: 234, Grantee: Durham Coco-Cola, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1930 March 1 (Box 6)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 101, Page: 40, Comments/Location: Milton Avenue & Buchanan
  - File No.: 235, Grantee: Standard Oil Company, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1932 June 14 (Box 6)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 105, Page: 223, Comments/Location: S/W Main Street
  - File No.: 236, Grantee: J. E. Underwood, Grantor: D.W. Newsom, Treasurer, Type: Deed, 2010 January 15 (Box 6)
    Deeds in the Real Estate Office are copies of public records, and are open for research. Additional materials under administrative restriction until 2035.
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 40, Page: 368421, Comments/Location: Onslow Street
  - File No.: 239, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Cornelius Thompson, Type: Deed, 1926 March 17 (Box 6)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 81, Page: 156
  - File No.: 240, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Frank Leathers, Type: Deed, 1926 March 17 (Box 6)
  - File No.: 241, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Frank Leathers, Type: Deed, 1926 June 30 (Box 6)
  - File No.: 242, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Damen Oliver, Type: Deed, 1926 May 1 (Box 6)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: Rowan
  - File No.: 243, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Maggie Miller, Type: Deed, 1926 August 21 (Box 6)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 83, Page: 608, Comments/Location: Rowan Alley
  - File No.: 244, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Edgar Thompson, Type: Deed, 1926 October 29 (Box 6)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 86, Page: 165, Comments/Location: Rowan Alley
  - File No.: 245, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Sallie Dixon, Type: Deed, 1926 November 1 (Box 6)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 86, Page: 164, Comments/Location: Rowan Alley
  - File No.: 246, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: R. B. Holeman, Type: Deed, 1927 February 10 (Box 6)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: Cook Street
  - File No.: 247, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: John E. Tilley, Type: Deed, 1927 February 11 (Box 6)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 85, Page: 112
  - File No.: 248, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: B. G. Proctor, Type: Deed, 1927 February 10 (Box 6)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 86, Page: 494, Comments/Location: Green Street
  - File No.: 249, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: R. T. Howerton, Type: Deed, 1927 February 7 (Box 6)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: Westover Park
  - File No.: 250, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Stephen S. Jones, Type: Deed, 1927 February 10 (Box 6)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: Along Southern RR
  - File No.: 251, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Charles Mayo, Type: Deed, 1927 May 12 (Box 6)
    County: Orange, Deed Book: 86, Page: 224, Comments/Location: Along Eno River
  - File No.: 252, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Charles Durham, Type: Deed, 1927 May 12 (Box 6)
    County: Orange, Comments/Location: Along Eno River
  - File No.: 253, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Jefferson Snipes & Others, Type: Deed, 1927 May 12 (Box 6)
    County: Orange, Deed Book: 86, Page: 226, Comments/Location: Along Eno River
  - File No.: 254, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Fred Wright, Type: Deed, 1927 May 12 (Box 6)
    County: Orange, Deed Book: 86, Page: 227, Comments/Location: Along Eno River
  - File No.: 255, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Thomas Mayo, Type: Deed, 1927 May 17 (Box 6)
    County: Orange, Deed Book: 86, Page: 228, Comments/Location: Line Along Eno River
  - File No.: 256, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Thomas Walker, Type: Deed, 1932 May 31 (Box 6)
    County: Orange, Deed Book: 99, Page: 80, Comments/Location: Thomas Walker Home Place
  - File No.: 257, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Dolian Harris, Type: Deed, 1929 April 27 (Box 6)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 95, Page: 479, Comments/Location: Medical Center Parking Garage II
  - File No.: 258, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Cornelius Brown, Type: Deed, 1930 November 11 (Box 6)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 100, Page: 62
  - File No.: 259, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Home Ins. Agency, Type: Deed, 1932 May 12 (Box 6)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: Erwin Road
  - File No.: 260, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: L. D. Kirkland, Type: Deed, 1932 April 30 (Box 6)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 106, Page: 437, Comments/Location: Cook Street
  - File No.: 261, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: W. L. Foushee, Type: Deed, 1932 April 29 (Box 6)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 105, Page: 132, Comments/Location: Erwin Road
  - File No.: 262, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: E. H. Clement, Type: Deed, 1932 November 16 (Box 6)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 107, Page: 109, Comments/Location: Erwin Road
  - File No.: 263, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: A. H. Graham, Comm, Type: Deed, 1933 January 16 (Box 6)
    County: Orange, Deed Book: 100, Page: 22, Comments/Location: Town of Hillsboro
  - File No.: 264, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Marshall Spears, Type: Deed, 1935 July 15 (Box 6)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 117, Page: 28, Comments/Location: Dover Street
  - File No.: 265, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Marshall Spears, Type: Deed, 1935 January 30 (Box 6)
    County: Orange, Deed Book: 103, Page: 117
  - File No.: 266, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: W. C. Yeargen, Type: Deed, 1935 December 18 (Box 6)
    County: Orange, Deed Book: 101, Page: 298, Comments/Location: Rigsbee Road
  - File No.: 267, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: E. C. McFarling, Type: Deed, 1934 January 9 (Box 6)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 110, Page: 115, Comments/Location: Atlas Street
  - File No.: 268, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Marshall Spears, Type: Deed, 1935 April 9 (Box 6)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 111, Page: 373, Comments/Location: Chapel Hill Road
  - File No.: 269, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Martin Tilley, Type: Deed, 1934 March 20 (Box 6)
    County: Orange, Deed Book: 102, Page: 27, Comments/Location: Chapel Hill Road
  - File No.: 270, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: W. T. Atkins, Type: Deed, 1935 July 16 (Box 6)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 117, Page: 32, Comments/Location: Cornwallis Road
  - File No.: 271, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Charles Skarren, Type: Deed, 1935 September 3 (Box 6)
    County: Carteret, Deed Book: 81, Page: 133, Comments/Location: Island in Beaufort Harbor
  - File No.: 272, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: H. F. Prytherch, Type: Deed, 1935 September 3 (Box 6)
    County: Carteret, Deed Book: 81, Page: 132, Comments/Location: Island in Beaufort Harbor
  - File No.: 273, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Murray Jones, Type: Deed, 1925 January 26 (Box 6)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 64, Page: 273
  - File No.: 274, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: James Moses, Type: Deed, 1936 April 3 (Box 6)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 118, Page: 18, Comments/Location: Mud Creek
  - File No.: 275, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: James Moses, Type: Deed, 1936 March 30 (Box 6)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 118, Page: 1, Comments/Location: Cornwallis Road
  - File No.: 276, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Martha Allen, Type: Deed, 1931 January 9 (Box 6)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 100, Page: 186, Comments/Location: Duke Homestead/Animal Farm Property
  - File No.: 277, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: George R. Newton, Type: Deed, 1932 September 1 (Box 6)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 106, Page: 613, Comments/Location: Chapel Hill & Snow Hill Road
  - File No.: 278, Grantee: Brady R. Jordan, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1931 August 31 (Box 6)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #29, Comments/Location: Pinecrest Road
  - File No.: 279, Grantee: Gilbert T. Rowe, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1931 October 28 (Box 6)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #2, Comments/Location: Pinecrest Road
  - File No.: 280, Grantee: Jay B. Hubbell, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1931 November 17 (Box 6)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 104, Page: 249, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #31, Comments/Location: Pinecrest Road
  - File No.: 281, Grantee: Alban G Widgery, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1931 December 5 (Box 7)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #1, Comments/Location: Pinecrest Road
  - File No.: 283, Grantee: W. C. Maxwell, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1932 January 28 (Box 7)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #6, Comments/Location: Pinecrest Road
  - File No.: 284, Grantee: Luther L. Gobbel, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1932 April 16 (Box 7)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #7, Comments/Location: Pinecrest Road
  - File No.: 285, Grantee: Archibald Jordan, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1932 September 2 (Box 7)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: Pinecrest Road
  - File No.: 286, Grantee: Alex Waite, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1933 March 29 (Box 7)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #5, Comments/Location: Pinecrest Road
  - File No.: 287, Grantee: Alex Waite, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1933 June 28 (Box 7)
  - File No.: 288, Grantee: Charles L. Haywood, Jr., Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1934 November 10 (Box 7)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: Anderson Street Extension
  - File No.: 289, Grantee: Alfred - Elizabeth Shands, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1934 November 20 (Box 7)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 114, Page: 95, Comments/Location: Anderson Street Extension
  - File No.: 290, Grantee: Watt W. Eagle, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1934 November 10 (Box 7)
  - File No.: 291, Grantee: Robert A. Ross, Grantor: Duke, Type: Letter, no Deed, 1938 April 20 (Box 7)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 114, Page: 96, Comments/Location: Anderson Street Extension
  - File No.: 292: Grantee: Lucius A Bigelow, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1934 November 20 (Box 7)
  - File No.: 293, Grantee: M. L. Black, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1935 August 29 (Box 7)
  - File No.: 294, Grantee: A. C. Jordan, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1935 May 8 (Box 7)
  - File No.: 295, Grantee: W. C. Maxwell, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1935 October 22 (Box 7)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: Land conveyed to W. C. Maxwell
  - File No.: 295, Grantee: W. C. Maxwell, Grantor: James P. Hendrix, Type: QC/Deed, 1949 January 31 (Box 7)
  - File No.: 296, Grantee: David W. Carpenter, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1936 June 23 (Box 7)
  - File No.: 297, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: John D. Biggs, Receiver, Type: Deed, 1936 December 5 (Box 7)
  - File No.: 297, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: J. B. Andrews, Type: QC/Deed, 1936 December 8 (Box 7)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 119, Page: 560, Comments/Location: Garfield Street
  - File No.: 298, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Doward Jones, Type: Deed, 1937 May 27 (Box 7)
  - File No.: 299, Grantee: Irwin Chesson, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1936 September 11 (Box 7)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: Swift Avenue
  - File No.: 300, Grantee: Irwin Chesson, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1937 January 15 (Box 7)
  - File No.: 301, Grantee: H. E. Myers, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1936 October 22 (Box 7)
  - File No.: 302, Grantee: Walter M. Nielsen, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1936 November 23 (Box 7)
  - File No.: 303, Grantee: Archibald C. Jordan, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1937 April 7 (Box 7)
  - File No.: 304, Grantee: Howard E. Jensen, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1937 April 15 (Box 7)
  - File No.: 305, Grantee: Everette B. Weatherspoon, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1937 May 8 (Box 7)
  - File No.: 306, Grantee: F. C. Owen, Trustee, Grantor: Duke, Type: Sub/Agrmnt, 1938 June 15 (Box 7)
  - File No.: 307, Grantee: Elbert L. Persons, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1937 May 27 (Box 7)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 120, Page: 522, Comments/Location: Anderson Street Extension
  - File No.: 308, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Erwin Cotton Mills, Type: Deed, 1926 June 3 (Box 7)
    County: Orange, Deed Book: 89, Page: 80, Comments/Location: On waters of New Hope Creek
  - File No.: 309, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Bert Cunningham, Type: Deed, 1925 August 20 (Box 7)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 78, Page: 315, Comments/Location: Buchanan & Markham Streets
  - File No.: 310, Grantee: City of Durham, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1928 November 22 (Box 7)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: Chapel Hill Street, Old/New File No.: 3003
  - File No.: 311, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: City of Durham, Type: Deed/Copy, 1930 November 7 (Box 7)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 76, Page: 468, Comments/Location: Anderson Street Extension
  - File No.: 312, Grantee: City of Durham, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1930 November 7 (Box 7)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: Mark Rigsbee Estate, Old/New File No.: 3004
  - File No.: 313, Grantee: City of Durham, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1930 November 7 (Box 7)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: Duke Univ. Road Pavement, Old/New File No.: 3005
  - File No.: 314, Grantee: City of Durham, Grantor: Duke, Type: QC/Deed, 1933 November 8 (Box 7)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: Along Erwin Road, Old/New File No.: 3006
  - File No.: 315, Grantee: City of Durham, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1933 November 29 (Box 7)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: Lakewood Park, Old/New File No.: 3007
  - File No.: 316, Grantee: City of Durham, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1930 November 14 (Box 7)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: Duke University Drive, Old/New File No.: 3008
  - File No.: 317, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Will Wilkins, Type: Deed, 1934 April 4 (Box 7)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: Wilkins Tract
  - File No.: 318, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: E.C. Garrard, Type: Abst/Title, 1937 August 16 (Box 7)
    County: Orange, Deed Book: 107, Page: 53, Comments/Location: New Hope Creek; 49 acres; title abstract
  - File No.: 319, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: W. K. Rand, Type: Deed, 1937 September 8 (Box 7)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 123, Page: 516, Comments/Location: W/S Swift Avenue
  - File No.: 320, Grantee: Robert R. Wilson, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed/Copy, 1937 July 8 (Box 7)